

# Chaudhry Ubaidullah Toor

manager.toor@gmail.com Phone: 03124375585 Address:

House No.4 Nadeem Town Multan Chungi Multan

Road Lahore

## Objective

"Success-driven team player who works well with marketing as well as research and development departments. Brings understanding of the sales funnel process and a willingness to work with everyone on the team to reach Company Goals."

### Work experience

**NBP FUNDS** 

Relationship Manager

May 2018 — March 2019 EDCONDS, Lahore

**Business Development Manager** 

State Life Insurance Corporation of

**Pakistan** 

Sales Representative

September 2014 — December 2016

May 2019 — September 2019

#### Education

November 2015 — March 2018 Master in Business Education

University of the Punjab

**MARKETING** 

**Bachelors** in Arts September 2011 — August 2013

University of the Punjab

Arabic, Islamic Studies, Persian

F.sc Pre-Medical September 2009 — August 2011

Jinnah Islamia College of Commerce

Biology, Physics, Chemistry

September 2007 — August 2009 Matriculation

Government Pilot Secondary School

Biology, Physics, Chemistry

# Qualifications

#### 1. English Communication Skills Course

Government College University Lahore (GC)

# Languages

- 1. Punjabi
- 2. Urdu
- 3. English

Chaudhry Ubaidullah Toor 2